Efe Asieghwu Gift Software Engineer | | Frontend developer

Q Lagos, Nigeria

≥ efeasiughu@gmail.com

08082284929

https://github.com/gift56

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/efe-gift-109120241/



Profile

I am a hardworking young Software Engineer focused on Frontend Development, with over two years(2+yrs) hands-on work experience with deep understanding of HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, ReactJS, Nextjs, Sass, TailwindCss and git.

I have reputation on getting things done and also I have the zeal on creating user-friendly interface websites, I am capable of handling any task given to me.

Experience

09/2022 – 11/2022 Abeokuta, Nigeria	Africa Trainovation Consulting, Frontend developer Internship ☑
05/2022 – 08/2022 Abeokuta, Nigeria	Cre8ng Freelance Job, Software Engineer (Frontend developer) ♂

Education		
Warri, Nigeria	Science Preparatory Centre (s.p.c), Secondary School ♂	
01/2022 – 07/2022 Abeokuta, Ogun state, Nigeria	Africa Trainovation Consulting, Software Engineer (Frontend Development)	

Skills

Computer programmer skills & Web • • • •	Interpersonal skills • • • • •			
development	Good Communication skills, problem solving and Analytics			
HTML5 CSS JAVASCRIPT SASS BOOTSTRAP				
REACT TAILWIND Styled-Components Git				

Achievements

- freeCodeCamp Javascript
 Argorithm and Data Structure
 Courses
- Frontend (Web Development Courses) at ATChub ☑

Languages

• English